Guide to the Robert Flaherty Film Seminar Archive 1949 - 2011 MSS.326
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Flaherty Film Seminars, 253680
  - Subseries A: Audio Recordings, 253681
    - 36th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, June 15, 1990; ID: 326.0495; 257258 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0495)
      Original Number: 1990-15
      Moderator Bo Smith Artist: Gyula Gazdag
      Discussion Moderator: Tom Johnson
    - 36th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, June 16, 1990; ID: 326.0496; 257259 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0496)
      Original Number: 1990-16
      Final Discussion Moderator: Tom Johnson
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, August 3, 1991; ID: 326.0497; 257265 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0497)
      Original Number: 1991-01
      "Auffengeil" Moderator: Richard Herkowitz Guests: Coco Fusco, Steve Gallager
      "Body Beautiful" "Desperate" Moderator: Coco Fusco
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, August 4, 1991; ID: 326.0498; 257266 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0498)
      Original Number: 1991-02
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, August 5, 1991; ID: 326.0499; 257267 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0499)
      Original Number: 1991-03
      New Brazilian Shorts Guests: Joao Luiz Vieira
      "Camera Arabe" Moderator: Steve Gallagher Guests: Ella Shohat
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, August 5, 1991; ID: 326.0500; 257268 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0500)
      Original Number: 1991-04
      "A Door is The Sky" Moderator: Coco Fusco Guests: Viola Shafir
      "Sights Unseen" "Work In Progress" "Un Chien Delicieux" "Tribulation 99" Moderator: Coco Fusco Guests: Luis Valdovino, Jonathan Robinson, Craig Baldwin, Ken Feingold
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, August 5, 1991; ID: 326.0501; 257269 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0501)
      Original Number: 1991-05
      "Chien Delivieux" "Space & Time" "Door To The Sky" Moderator: Faye Ginsberg Roddy Bogawa- "Some Divine Wind Rea [Tiddiri]- "History and Memory"
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 5, 1991; ID: 326.0502; 257270 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0502)
      Original Number: 1991-06
      "History & Memory" "Some Divine Wind" Moderator: Faye Ginsburg Guests: Red Tajliri, Roddy Bogwawa
      "Permissible Dreams" "Omar Gatlato" Moderator: Coco Fusco Guests: Viola Alia Arasoughly
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, August 6, 1991; ID: 326.0503; 257271 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0503)
      Original Number: 1991-07
      "Once Upon a Time in the Bronx" "Rap City Rhapsody" "Fade to Black" Moderator: Steve Gallagher Guests: Ela Troyano, Don Trammel
      "Urinal" "The Making of 'Monsters'" Guests: John Greyson
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, August 6, 1991; ID: 326.0504; 257272 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0504)
      Original Number: 1991-08
      Introduction & "Louisiana Story" by Bill Sloan
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, August 6, 1991; ID: 326.0505; 257273 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0505)
      Original Number: 1991-09
      "Making of 'Monsters'" "Urinal" Guests: John Greyson
      "Fertile Memories" Moderator: Ella Shohat, Viola Shafik
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, August 7, 1991; ID: 326.0506; 257274 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0506)
      Original Number: 1991-10
      "I Need Your Full Cooperation" "Interpretation of Dreams" Moderator: Patty Zimmerman Guests: Andrei Zagdansky, Kathy High
      "I Need Your Full Cooperation: "Interpretation of Dreams" Moderator: Patty Zimmerman Guests: Andrei Zagdansky, Kathy High
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, August 7, 1991; ID: 326.0507; 257278 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0507)
      Original Number: 1991-11
      "Plastic Jesus" Moderator: Erik Barnouw Guests: Lazar Stojanovic
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, August 8, 1991; ID: 326.0508; 257279 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0508)
      Original Number: 1991-12
      "Canticle of Stones" Moderator: Viola Shatik Guests: Ella Shohat, Viola Shatik
      "Intifada: The Introduction to An End of An Argument" "Speaking for Oneself-Sepaking for Others" Moderator: Viola Shatik Guests: Ella Shohat
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, 1991; ID: 326.0509; 257280 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0509)
      Original Number: 1991-13
      "Measure of Distance" Elia Suleiman
      "Symbiophychotaxiplasm: Take One" William Greaves Jakkie
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, August 8, 1991; ID: 326.0510; 257281 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0510)
      Original Number: 1991-14
      William Greaves "Symbiopychotaxiplasm:Take One" Moderator: Jackie
    - 37th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, August 9, 1991; ID: 326.0511; 257282 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0511)
      Original Number: 1991-15
      "Pay Any Means Necessary" "Mysteries of July" Moderator: Patty Zimmerman, Richard Horskowitz
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, August 8, 1992; ID: 326.0512; 257275 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0512, Case 326.0512)
      Original Number: 1992-01
      Opening: Tom Johson "Brother's Keeper" Joe Berlinger
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, August 9, 1992; ID: 326.0513; 257285 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0513)
      Original Number: 1992-02
      "Bullets for Breakfast" Molly Fisher
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, August 9, 1992; ID: 326.0514; 257286 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0514)
      Original Number: 1992-03
      Intro: Scott MacDonald Dis. Reggio & Porter
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, August 10, 1992; ID: 326.0515; 257287 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0515)
      Original Number: 1992-04
      Scott MacDonald Ken Jacobs
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, August 10, 1992; ID: 326.0516; 257288 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0516)
      Original Number: 1992-05
      Wille Verella/Chris Wellsby Cheryl Dunye
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 10, 1992; ID: 326.0517; 257289 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0517)
      Original Number: 1992-06
      "Vinh" Keiko Tsuno
      Cheryl Dunye
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, August 11, 1992; ID: 326.0518; 257290 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0518)
      Original Number: 1992-07
      "Emperor's Naked Army" Interview with Kazuo Hara
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, August 11, 1992; ID: 326.0519; 257291 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0519)
      Original Number: 1992-08
      interview with Keiko Tsuno "Vinh"
      Interview with Kazuo Hara "Emperor's Naked Army"
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, August 11, 1992; ID: 326.0520; 257292 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0520)
      Original Number: 1992-09
      Tom Johnson intro to "Brother's Keeper"
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, August 12, 1992; ID: 326.0521; 257293 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0521)
      Original Number: 1992-10
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, August 12, 1992; ID: 326.0522; 257294 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0522)
      Original Number: 1992-11
      Portia Cobb
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, 1992; ID: 326.0523; 257295 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0523)
      Original Number: 1992-12
      Portia Cobb/Willie
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, August 13, 1992; ID: 326.0524; 257296 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0524)
      Original Number: 1992-13
      Willie
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, August 13, 1992; ID: 326.0525; 257297 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0525)
      Original Number: 1992-14
      Ed Radtke & Jeff Wray
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, August 13, 1992; ID: 326.0526; 257298 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0526)
      Original Number: 1992-15
      Camille Billops & James Hatch
      Camille Billops & James Hatch/Willie
    - 38th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, August 14, 1992; ID: 326.0527; 257299 (Box 11, Media ID: 326.0527, Case 326.0527)
      Original Number: 1992-16
      Wrap-up
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, August 7, 1993; ID: 326.0528; 257302 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0528)
      Original Number: 1993-01
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, August 8, 1993; ID: 326.0529; 257303 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0529)
      Original Number: 1993-02
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, August 8, 1993; ID: 326.0530; 257304 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0530, Case 326.0530)
      Original Number: 1993-03
      Leighton Pierce et. al
      Juan Downey Meena
      Access CD available
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, August 8, 1993; ID: 326.0531; 257305 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0531)
      Original Number: 1993-04
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, August 8, 1993; ID: 326.0532; 257306 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0532)
      Original Number: 1993-05
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 9, 1993; ID: 326.0533; 257307 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0533)
      Original Number: 1993-06
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, August 9, 1993; ID: 326.0534; 257308 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0534)
      Original Number: 1993-07
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, August 9, 1993; ID: 326.0535; 257309 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0535)
      Original Number: 1993-08
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, August 9, 1993; ID: 326.0536; 257310 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0536)
      Original Number: 1993-09
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, August 10, 1993; ID: 326.0537; 257311 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0537)
      Original Number: 1993-10
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, August 10, 1993; ID: 326.0538; 257312 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0538)
      Original Number: 1993-11
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, August 10, 1993; ID: 326.0539; 257313 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0539)
      Original Number: 1993-12
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, August 11, 1993; ID: 326.0540; 257314 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0540)
      Original Number: 1993-13
      Moderator: Margarita de la Vega Hurtado
      Kidnapping of Sylia Motta, daughter of Bogota industrialist [Panal/carway] by filmmaker/sisiter of kidnapped victim and cinematogrpaher
      filmmaker Camila Hotta
      Access CD available. Ask for parts 1 and 2.
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, August 11, 1993; ID: 326.0541; 257315 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0541)
      Original Number: 1993-14
      Marta Rodriguez with Margarita de la Vega Hurtado & Christopher Ortiz
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, August 11, 1993; ID: 326.0542; 257316 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0542)
      Original Number: 1993-15
      John Akomfrah with June Givani
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, August 12, 1993; ID: 326.0543; 257317 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0543)
      Original Number: 1993-16
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, August 12, 1993; ID: 326.0544; 257319 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0544)
      Original Number: 1993-17
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, August 12, 1993; ID: 326.0545; 257323 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0545)
      Original Number: 1993-18
      Discussion wrap-up
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 19, 1993; ID: 326.0546; 257320 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0546)
      Original Number: 1993-19
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 20, August 13, 1993; ID: 326.0547; 257321 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0547)
      Original Number: 1993-20
    - 39th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 21, 1993; ID: 326.0548; 257322 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0548, Case 326.0548)
      Original Number: 1993-21
      Juan Downey
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, August 6, 1994; ID: 326.0549; 257403 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0549)
      Original Number: 1994-01
      Saturday Night Intros
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, August 7, 1994; ID: 326.0550; 257404 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0550)
      Original Number: 1994-02
      Contents unknown.
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, August 7, 1994; ID: 326.0551; 257406 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0551)
      Original Number: 1994-03
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, August 7, 1994; ID: 326.0552; 257408 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0552)
      Original Number: 1994-04
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, 1994; ID: 326.0553; 257410 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0553)
      Original Number: 1994-05
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 8, 1994; ID: 326.0554; 257412 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0554)
      Original Number: 1994-06
      Nick Deo Campo
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, 1994; ID: 326.0555; 257415 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0555)
      Original Number: 1994-07
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, 1994; ID: 326.0556; 257417 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0556)
      Original Number: 1994-08
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, 1994; ID: 326.0557; 257419 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0557)
      Original Number: 1994-09
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, 1994; ID: 326.0558; 257422 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0558)
      Original Number: 1994-10
      Uski Roti
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, 1994; ID: 326.0559; 257423 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0559)
      Original Number: 1994-11
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, 1994; ID: 326.0560; 257427 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0560)
      Original Number: 1994-12
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, August 10, 1994; ID: 326.0561; 257430 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0561)
      Original Number: 1994-13
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, August 10, 1994; ID: 326.0562; 257431 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0562)
      Original Number: 1994-14
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, August 11, 1994; ID: 326.0563; 257432 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0563)
      Original Number: 1994-15
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, August 11, 1994; ID: 326.0564; 257433 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0564)
      Original Number: 1994-16
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, 1994; ID: 326.0565; 257434 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0565)
      Original Number: 1994-17
      Dhrupad
    - 40th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, August 11, 1994; August 12, 1994; ID: 326.0566; 257435 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0566)
      Original Number: 1994-18
      Siddeshwari
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, 1996; ID: 326.0567; 257436 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0567)
      Original Number: 1996-01
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, 1996; ID: 326.0568; 257437 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0568)
      Original Number: 1996-02
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, 1996; ID: 326.0569; 257438 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0569)
      Original Number: 1996-03
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, 1996; ID: 326.0570; 257439 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0570)
      Original Number: 1996-04
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, August 4, 1996; ID: 326.0571; 257440 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0571)
      Original Number: 1996-05
      Dratfield Brunch
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 6, 1996; ID: 326.0572; 257441 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0572)
      Original Number: 1996-06
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, 1996; ID: 326.0573; 257442 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0573)
      Original Number: 1996-07
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, 1996; ID: 326.0574; 257443 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0574)
      Original Number: 1996-08
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, 1996; ID: 326.0575; 257444 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0575)
      Original Number: 1996-09
      Kuchar/Vasulka
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, 1996; ID: 326.0576; 257445 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0576)
      Original Number: 1996-10
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, August 1996; ID: 326.0577; 257447 (Box 12, Media ID: 326.0577)
      Original Number: 1996-11
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, August, 1996; ID: 326.0578; 257451 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0578)
      Original Number: 1996-12
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, August, 1996; ID: 326.0579; 257452 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0579)
      Original Number: 1996-13
      Contents Unknown.
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, August 7, 1996; August 8, 1996; ID: 326.0580; 257453 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0580)
      Original Number: 1996-14
      Merata Blessing
    - 42nd Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, August 8, 1996; ID: 326.0581; 257454 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0581)
      Original Number: 1996-15
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 01, August 7, 1998; ID: 326.0582; 257455 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0582)
      Original Number: 1999-01
      Wachsmann and Rosenblatt
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, August 7, 1998; ID: 326.0583; 257456 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0583)
      Original Number: 1998-01
      Wachsman, Rosenblatt/Mandel
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, August 8, 1998; ID: 326.0584; 257457 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0584)
      Original Number: 1998-02
      Peter Forgacs A.M. Session
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, August 8, 1998; ID: 326.0585; 257458 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0585)
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, August 8, 1998; ID: 326.0586; 257459 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0586)
      Original Number: 1998-03
      McLean and Marcovich afternoon session
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, August 8, 1998; ID: 326.0587; 257460 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0587)
      Sienna McLean and Carlos Marcovich Afternoon
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, August 8, 1998; ID: 326.0588; 257461 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0588)
      Original Number: 1998-04
      Ning Ying
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, August 8, 1998; ID: 326.0589; 257462 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0589)
      Ning Ying P.M. Discussion
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, August 9, 1998; ID: 326.0590; 257463 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0590)
      Original Number: 1998-05
      Hillel Tryster
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, August 9, 1998; ID: 326.0591; 257464 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0591)
      Hillel Tryster (Spielberg Archive)
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, August 9, 1998; ID: 326.0592; 257465 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0592)
      Hillel Tryster (duplicate)
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 9, 1998; ID: 326.0593; 257466 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0593)
      Original Number: 1998-06
      Kore-Eda Hirokazu Afternoon
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, August 9, 1998; ID: 326.0594; 257467 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0594)
      Kore-Eda
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, August 9, 1998; ID: 326.0595; 257468 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0595)
      Original Number: 1998-07
      Peter Forgacs night session
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, August 9, 1998; ID: 326.0596; 257469 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0596)
      Peter Forgacs
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, August 10, 1998; ID: 326.0597; 257470 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0597)
      Original Number: 1998-08
      Ning Ying morning
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, August 10, 1998; ID: 326.0598; 257471 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0598)
      Original Number: 1998-09
      Afternoon [Contents Unknown]
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, August 10, 1998; ID: 326.0599; 257472 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0599)
      Monday afternoon, Forgas
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, August 10, 1998; ID: 326.0600; 257473 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0600)
      Original Number: 1998-10
      Kore-eda Hirozaku - Evening
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, August 11, 1998; ID: 326.0601; 257474 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0601)
      Original Number: 1998-11
      Rosenblatt/ Friedrich tape one
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, August 11, 1998; ID: 326.0602; 257475 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0602)
      Original Number: 1998-12
      Rosenblatt / Friedrich tape two
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 13, 1998; ID: 326.0603; 257476 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0603)
      Original Number: 1998-13
      Ilan Ziv and Daoud Kuttab
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 14, [undated]; ID: 326.0604; 257488 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0604)
      Original Number: 1998-14
      Kore Eda
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 15, August 12, 1998; ID: 326.0605; 257490 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0605)
      Original Number: 1998-15
      Loni Ding - Afternoon session,
      Moderator: Barbara Abrash
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 16, August 12, 1998; ID: 326.0606; 257491 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0606)
      Original Number: 1998-16
      W. Raad and P. Forgacs - Evening
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 17, August 13, 1998; ID: 326.0607; 257492 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0607)
      Original Number: 1998-17
      Flaherty Closing Discussion
    - 44th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 18, August 13, 1998; ID: 326.0608; 257493 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0608)
      Original Number: 1998-18
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 1, June 5, 1999; ID: 326.0609; 257494 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0609)
      Original Format: Panasonic DAT
      Intro remarks, Mississippi eyes, 6.5 morning session, Jason Livingston,
      Orlando Bagwell, Flaherty, Duke University
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 2, June 5, 1999; ID: 326.0610; 257495 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0610)
      Original Format: Sony DAT
      Original Number: 1999-02
      Moderator: Orlando Bagwell
      Jeanie Jordon, John Else, Group Introductions, recorded by Jack Farrish and Rob Koegler
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 3, June 5, 1999; ID: 326.0611; 257496 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0611)
      Original Number: 1999-03
      Opening Remarks: Orlando Bagwell "Four Little Girls" Jackie
      Discussion Moderator: Sam Pollard
      Recorded by Jack Parrish and Rob Koegler
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 4, June 5, 1999; ID: 326.0612; 257497 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0612)
      Original Number: 1999-04
      Intro Remarks, Richard Herskowitz, Peleshian: The End, Inhabitants Our City,
      T with discussion, Translator: Boris
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 5, June 6, 1999; ID: 326.0613; 257498 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0613)
      Original Number: 1999-05
      Flaherty, Duke University
      Intro Remarks: Richard Herskowitz, Louisiana Story, Study Film, Richard "Ricky" Leacook,
      and Discussion moderatred by R. Herskowitz
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 6, June 6, 1999; ID: 326.0614; 257499 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0614)
      Original Number: 1999-06
      Flaherty, Duke University Afternoon Intro Remarks R. Herskowitz David Simpson and Discussion with David Simpson
      Moderated by R. Herskowtiz
      Noblessa Oblige Halstend St
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 7, June 7, 1999; ID: 326.0615; 257500 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0615)
      Original Number: 1999-07
      Evening session, Intro Remarks, Herskowitz, Van der Keuken Global Village, Discussion Johann Van der Keuken, Moderator: Richard Herskowitz
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 8, June 7, 1999; ID: 326.0616; 257502 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0616)
      Original Number: 1999-08
      Morning: Ricky Leacock, Holga video, French TV sequence, clip from SIberian and discussion,
      Afternoon: Intro: Jane Gaines, Lucy Massie Phenix, Elizabeth Barrett, Stranger with a camera, and discussion with Lucy Phenix and Elizabeth Barrett, Moderator: Jane Gaines
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 9, June 7, 1999; ID: 326.0617; 257507 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0617)
      Original Number: 1999-09
      End of discussion with Elizabeth Barrett and Lucy Phenix moderated by Jane Gaines, Evening, Intro R. Herskowitz, David Williams
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 10, June 7, 1999; ID: 326.0618; 257508 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0618)
      Original Number: 1999-10
      Filmmaker: David Williams, Moderator: Recording: Rob Koegler
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 11, June 8, 1999; ID: 326.0619; 257509 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0619)
      Original Number: 1999-11
      Intro Remarks: Orlando Bagwell, John Else, Cadillac Desert,
      Discussion: John Else, Moderator: Orlando Bagwell, Recording: Rob Koegler
    - 45th Annual Flaherty Seminar - Tape 12, June 8, 1999; ID: 326.0620; 257510 (Box 13, Media ID: 326.0620)
      Original Number: 1999-12
      Evening Session: The first half of the opening remarks can be found on videotape, the second half of the opening remarks are here.